bristowgroup.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - bristowgroup.com

Dapibus tempor turpis nisi et ultricies magnis. Nascetur et enim eros ac rhoncus vut facilisis risus.

Bristow Group adheres to the highest standards and applicable law to maintain the privacy of personal information that may be collected at this website. When you provide any of the information described in this Privacy Statement (including information that may be automatically generated), you consent to the use and disclosure of that information as described by this statement. This privacy statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that Bristow Group does not own or control, or to individuals that Bristow Group does not employ or manage. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our site. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

## User Generated Information 

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. Bristow Group will retain your contact information (such as name and email address) only if you contact us, for the purposes of responding to your inquiry. If you e-mail us, you are voluntarily releasing the content of your e-mail to us (including your e-mail address). 

## Automatic Information 

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Bristow Group automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Bristow Group cookie information, and the page you requested. Bristow Group uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the site. Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components. This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often visitors use parts of the site. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Bristow Group’s cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are.

## How Information is Used and Shared 

Bristow Group does not share any personal information on site visitors, except when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Bristow Group, our employees, our visitors, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone.

## Links to Other Sites 

For your convenience, this page may contain certain hyperlinks to other websites. While Bristow Group's website is subject to this privacy statement, we can make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages and sites that are not owned by Bristow Group. We therefore recommend that you read the privacy statement for each third party site you visit.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement 

Bristow Group may amend this Privacy Statement. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our web site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

## Information Security

Bristow Group uses commercially reasonable methods consistent with industry practice to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure appropriate use of your personal information. 

## Contact Us 

If you have any questions, comments, suggestions on how we can make this website more useful, please contact us at [webmaster@bristowgroup.com](mailto:webmaster@bristowgroup.com).
